[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "think", "as", "a", "host", ",", "if", "I", "say", "this", "is", "what", "I", "want", "to", "talk", "about", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "we", "should", "address", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "Not really, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Christine O'Donnell, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Christine", "O'Donnell", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "I'm doing well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine O'Donnell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "You can be both, can't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "be", "both", ",", "ca", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "When you look back on it, what was the catalyst, do you think, or -- not your down fall but your hiccup?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "on", "it", ",", "what", "was", "the", "catalyst", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "or", "--", "not", "your", "down", "fall", "but", "your", "hiccup", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CC", ":", "RB", "PRP$", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Well, I think -- I like the way you say it's a hiccup.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "like", "the", "way", "you", "say", "it", "'s", "a", "hiccup", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "How can you be a witch?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "you", "be", "a", "witch", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Because I dabbled into witchcraft.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "dabbled", "into", "witchcraft", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Your first date was in the satanic altar?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "first", "date", "was", "in", "the", "satanic", "altar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "I would have thought there was a pretty good chance that you could make a pretty big move back into the political stage, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "would", "have", "thought", "there", "was", "a", "pretty", "good", "chance", "that", "you", "could", "make", "a", "pretty", "big", "move", "back", "into", "the", "political", "stage", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Well, I hope to stay in the political arena -- maybe not necessarily as a candidate or in an elected office.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "hope", "to", "stay", "in", "the", "political", "arena", "--", "maybe", "not", "necessarily", "as", "a", "candidate", "or", "in", "an", "elected", "office", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "The problem, Christine, if I may just jump in there?", "question_tokens": ["The", "problem", ",", "Christine", ",", "if", "I", "may", "just", "jump", "in", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "RB", "VB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Do you still think masturbation is wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "think", "masturbation", "is", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Let's not even go there.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "not", "even", "go", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Catholic Church"]}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "So, am I right in assuming your views have evolved over the years?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "am", "I", "right", "in", "assuming", "your", "views", "have", "evolved", "over", "the", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Well, I am a practicing Catholic and I support what the Catholic Church teaches.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "am", "a", "practicing", "Catholic", "and", "I", "support", "what", "the", "Catholic", "Church", "teaches", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "RB", "VB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Can I ask you, have you -- have you committed lust in your heart and therefore adultery?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "ask", "you", ",", "have", "you", "--", "have", "you", "committed", "lust", "in", "your", "heart", "and", "therefore", "adultery", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Let's not even go there.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "not", "even", "go", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "-- what is your view of gay marriage, for example?", "question_tokens": ["--", "what", "is", "your", "view", "of", "gay", "marriage", ",", "for", "example", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "I address that stuff in the book.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "address", "that", "stuff", "in", "the", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "-- I obviously want to talk about the issues that I choose to talk about in the book.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "obviously", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "the", "issues", "that", "I", "choose", "to", "talk", "about", "in", "the", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Do you answer that question in the book?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "answer", "that", "question", "in", "the", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "I talk about my religious beliefs, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "talk", "about", "my", "religious", "beliefs", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "So, I'm bemused as to why you wouldn't just say it in an interview if it's in the book?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "I", "'m", "bemused", "as", "to", "why", "you", "would", "n't", "just", "say", "it", "in", "an", "interview", "if", "it", "'s", "in", "the", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Because I don't think it's relevant.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "relevant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "You should restore that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "should", "restore", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "I'm not talking policies.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "talking", "policies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Why are you being so weird about this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "being", "so", "weird", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "I'm not being weird about this, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "being", "weird", "about", "this", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "think", "as", "a", "host", ",", "if", "I", "say", "this", "is", "what", "I", "want", "to", "talk", "about", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "we", "should", "address", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Not really, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["6:00"]}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "You're leaving?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "leaving", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "Well, I was supposed to be speaking at the Republican women's club at 6:00, and I chose to be a little late for that not to be -- you know, yes, not to endure rude talk show hosts, but to talk to you about my book and to talk about the issues that I address in my book.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "supposed", "to", "be", "speaking", "at", "the", "Republican", "women", "'s", "club", "at", "6:00", ",", "and", "I", "chose", "to", "be", "a", "little", "late", "for", "that", "not", "to", "be", "--", "you", "know", ",", "yes", ",", "not", "to", "endure", "rude", "talk", "show", "hosts", ",", "but", "to", "talk", "to", "you", "about", "my", "book", "and", "to", "talk", "about", "the", "issues", "that", "I", "address", "in", "my", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Have you read the book?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "read", "the", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Yes, but these issues are in your book.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "these", "issues", "are", "in", "your", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Are we done?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "He's still there.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "still", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "What do you hope to achieve here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "hope", "to", "achieve", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't characterize it as aggressive when you consider the sense of urgency that I think we all need to have about the crisis of confidence that exists in our country as a result of a crisis of leadership.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "characterize", "it", "as", "aggressive", "when", "you", "consider", "the", "sense", "of", "urgency", "that", "I", "think", "we", "all", "need", "to", "have", "about", "the", "crisis", "of", "confidence", "that", "exists", "in", "our", "country", "as", "a", "result", "of", "a", "crisis", "of", "leadership", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "So there's a real disparity here between I think big, successful companies like yours, like McDonald's, like Apple and so on, and what is happening to the average guy on the street, isn't there?", "question_tokens": ["So", "there", "'s", "a", "real", "disparity", "here", "between", "I", "think", "big", ",", "successful", "companies", "like", "yours", ",", "like", "McDonald", "'s", ",", "like", "Apple", "and", "so", "on", ",", "and", "what", "is", "happening", "to", "the", "average", "guy", "on", "the", "street", ",", "is", "n't", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNP", "POS", ",", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, I think unfortunately the gap between the rich and poor, and the haves and have nots has widened.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "unfortunately", "the", "gap", "between", "the", "rich", "and", "poor", ",", "and", "the", "haves", "and", "have", "nots", "has", "widened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["McDonald's", "Apple"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2008"]}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Tell me about that period and about what you did to get Starbucks back on fire again?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "that", "period", "and", "about", "what", "you", "did", "to", "get", "Starbucks", "back", "on", "fire", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Well, the irony is when I came back in 2008, it was terrible timing because it was during the cataclysmic financial crisis.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "irony", "is", "when", "I", "came", "back", "in", "2008", ",", "it", "was", "terrible", "timing", "because", "it", "was", "during", "the", "cataclysmic", "financial", "crisis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "What parallels do you see with America incorporated?", "question_tokens": ["What", "parallels", "do", "you", "see", "with", "America", "incorporated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "First off, I want to be extremely respectful of Congress and the president.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "off", ",", "I", "want", "to", "be", "extremely", "respectful", "of", "Congress", "and", "the", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "You're doing your homework.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "doing", "your", "homework", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110817pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "But I didn't know -- how did you find that out about the China Club?", "question_tokens": ["But", "I", "did", "n't", "know", "--", "how", "did", "you", "find", "that", "out", "about", "the", "China", "Club", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "I have spies everywhere.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "spies", "everywhere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["China Club"]}}]